# 一直看街上有卖的 但是从来不知道怎么做的
Always see it sold on street, but don’t know how to make it
# 怎么形成的不知道
I don’t know how to make it
# 对
Yeah
# 要擀成1毫米的厚度
Rolled it into one millimeter thick
# 擀得跟纸一样
Like paper
# 雪鱼现在在徐州 待会我们要解决一下自己的早餐问题
Xueyu are in xuzhou now, we need to have some breakfast
# 在徐州当地 有一种比较特色的主食 面食 烙馍
There is a famous staple food in Xuzhou called “lao mo”
# 这个名字听了好久了 我待会呢 打算就是
I heard this name a lot times, I will
# 吃一个沓烙馍 用烙馍加上鸡蛋来吃
Eat a “ta lao mo” which is “lao mo” with egg
# 去看看这种特色的美食是什么样的吧
Let’s take a look
# 我们今天的目的地是在一个小院子里
We come to a small yard now
# 一饼一蛋5块钱 一饼两蛋6块钱
A “lao mo” with an egg is 5 yuan, and a “lao mo” with two eggs is 6 yuan
# 两个饼一个蛋的
Two “lao mo” with an egg
# 辣椒要不要  我要微辣的
Do you want spicy pepper? A little spicy is fine
# 在这儿吃
For there
# 来 给美女送去
Give it to the  beautiful lady
# 还没找到地方呢
We haven’t found our seats yet
# 屋里面 屋里面有地方
There are seats in the room
# 烙馍都是提前做好的
“Lao mo” are precooked
# 客人点完就可以吃到
Customers can eat it immediately after ordering
# 咱们这个是两个饼一个蛋6块钱
Two “lao mo” and an egg is 6 yuan
# 刚做出来的沓馍是又薄又脆的
Fresh “ta Lao mo” is thin and crispy
# 吃一口渣渣掉的哪里都是
A single bite and the crumbs are everywhere
# 咱们里面是加了葱花和一点点的辣椒的
There are some chopped green onion and few spicy pepper
# 这么一尝 是有点油酥饼的意思的
It tastes like “ you su bing”
# 不过会比它更脆 因为更薄嘛
But it's more crispy because it's thinner
# 我在这里吃烙馍没有要汤
I didn’t order the soup for “lao mo”
# 刚才阿姨进来的时候说
That’s why the aunt asked me
# 要不要喝的 我帮你免费盛一碗
If I want a soup, and she can give me for free
# 真是太感谢阿姨了
Thanks for her
# 这就是烙馍 徐州的 只有徐州有
This is “lao mo”. I can only be found in Xuzhou
# 其他地方有类似的小吃 叫法不一样
There is similar street food in other cities but with different name
# 徐州吃煎饼也蛮多的
“Jian bing” is also popular in Xuzhou
# 大哥说 下次我来的时候 给我做一个超脆的
Big brother said he gonna make me a super crispy “lao mo” when I come here next time
# 我说 超脆的和普通的有什么样的区别
I ask, what’s the differences?
# 他说 超脆的是3个饼皮
He said super crispy ones have three layers
# 像这样的饼就是3张饼皮 超脆
Like this, super crispy
# 这样的厚一点
This are thicker
# 这边最忙的时候 能卖多少馍
How many “lao mo” are sold every day? When it's at the peak
# 换算成饼 800多张吧
About 800 slices
# 光馍800多张
About 800 “lao mo”?
# 做成的话就是不到400份
Not more than 400
# 400份吧
About 400
# 没有四百份 三四百份
300 to 400
# 平时用60多斤烙馍
About 60 pound of dough
# 一斤有10张烙馍 做好卖300多份
A pound of dough can make 10 slices ”lao mo”
# 时间很短
In a short time
# 大哥做烙馍 切开的时候一定要像搭积木这样放吗
Big brother do you have to build it as Lego after slicing it?
# 立起来放的原因是 这样有利于通风
The reason to put it standing is too allow good ventilation
# 通风里面才会脆
Ventilation makes it crispy
# 把里面的热气排出来以后 它就会脆了
It gets crispy after the hot air inside comes out
# 这是最重要的
This is the most important step
# 只有脆的馍才能立起来 立起来的也会更脆
Only crispy “lao mo” can stand, and standing makes it more crispy
# 大哥不仅在介绍自己的烙馍
Big brother introduces not just his “lao mo”
# 还向我们介绍徐州的其它小吃
but also other street foods in Xuzhou
# 比如说蛙鱼 把子肉 等等
Like "wa yu", “ba zi rou “ and so on
# 中午是把子肉和各种炒菜
“Ba zi rou: and plenty of stir fry dishes served at lunch
# 晚上在徐州就是吃羊肉串
kebab is eaten in the evening in Xuzhou
# 蛮厉害
Very good
# 都是美味
All delicious
#我蛮困的，可能有些翻译的不是特别准确，麻烦多多包涵